

CLAUDIO MARTINOL

via Montegrappa 30, 21020, Casciago (Varese, Italy)

(+39) 3482915297

claudiomartinoli96@gmail.com

I'm 27, in the IT consultancy field since 2019. During the first years of my career I worked on two projects for some of the most important clients for my company (Eniservizi and Kone elevators). In 2022 I chose to work for a production company and I got hired in Axiotek where I followed design, planning and development of the software embedded in the new generation of durometers. Since a web interface was needed, I started learning Angular to develop a web app. In order to get better with those new skills I decided to find a position as full stack developer, discovering Akkodis where I am currently employed.

WORK EXPERIENCE

15 sept. 2023 - ongoing

Advanced ICT Consultant

Akkodis (Milano, Italy)

Customer

Prometeia

Market

Finance and Servicies

Technologies

Angular, .Net, SQL Server, C#, IIS, SMSS, Git, Tortoise. Jira

Activities

Development and management of risk evaluation software for numerous banks around the world

Technical consulting Incident management

Angular Development and maintenance Web Api maintenance and development Design and development of change requests and new functionalities

12 sept. 2022 - 15 sept. 2023

Solution Developer

Axiotek SRL (Varese, Italy)

Activities

Design, planning and development of full stack application to run MX3000 durometer

Technologies used

WPF C#, Postgress SQL, Angular, Git

Design patterns used

Model View View Model, sigleton, factory

1 sept. 2019 - 9 sept. 2022

Solution Developer

Engineering Ingegneria Informatica (Milano, Italy)

Customer

Kone Elevators

Market

Infrastructure and Services

Technologies

BMC Remedy, .Net, SQL Server, C#, IIS, SMSS

Activities

Technical consulting

Incident management

Managing ITSM applications

Performance monitoring and optimization design and development of change requests and new functionalities

Development of Integration services on .Net (SQL, C#) framework

Design and development of desktop applications using windows forms and WPF Java

13 jan 2019 - 25 jul. 2019

Infrastructure Engineer

Engineering DHUB (Milano, Italy)

Customer

Eni S.P.A.

Market

Energy and utilities

Technologies

Java, Oracle SQL

Activities

Technical consulting Managing trouble ticketing software Service Manager 9 on behalf of ENI S.P.A.

EDUCATION

Liceo Scientifico Vittorio Sereni

Science degree (via Lugano 24, Luino, 21016, Italy)

Field of study: Natural sience, mathematics

and statistics

Final grade: 77/100

Learned professional skills:

English

Mathematics, physics, C Programming and

Pascal

Use of Microsoft office suite

ICT School Enrico Della Valle Engineering SpA

Training courses (Via Casilina 246, 03013, Ferentino, Italy)

10-14 nov 2019

Professional training course "Oracle SQL"

15-19 dic 2019

Professional training course "Microsoft SQL SERVER"

6-10 giu 2021

Professional training course "SQL Server Integration Services"

8-12 nov 2021

Professional training course "Visual Studio:

Programming in C# - Specialist"

20-24 giu 2022

Professional training course "Object oriented design"

11-16 lug 2022

Professional training course "Design thinking foundation"

Ander Matine

LANGUAGES

ITALIAN

Fluent

ENGLISH

Spoken (B2)

Written (C1)